SPACE.
IT SEEMS
TO GO ON AND ON FOREVER
BUT THEN YOU GET TO THE END
AND A GORILLA STARTS
THROWING BARRELS AT YOU.
AND THAT'S
HOW YOU PLAY THE GAME.
YOU STINK. LOSER.
HEY. FRY!
PIZZA GOING OUT.
COME ON!
[ Sighs ]
TSK. TSK. TSK.
[ Revelers Shouting.
Laughing ]
MICHELLE. BABY.
WHERE YOU GOING?
IT'S NOT WORKING OUT. FRY.
I PUT YOUR STUFF OUT
ON THE SIDEWALK!
I HATE MY LIFE.
I HATE MY LIFE. I HATE MY LIFE.
[ Distant Laughter ]
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
HELLO!
PIZZA DELIVERY!
FOR. UH...
"I.C. WIENER"?
OH. CRUD.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
BY THIS POINT IN MY LIFE
I'D BE THE ONE
MAKING THE CRANK CALLS.
HERE'S TO ANOTHER
LOUSY MILLENNIUM.
[ Crowd ]
TEN!
NEUF!
OTTO!
SABAA!
EKSI!
WU!
CHAAR!
THATHU!
NI!
ONE!
[ Screams ]
WHAT TH--
[ Gasping ]
[ Groaning ]
WHEW.
[ Gasps ]
MY GOD.
IT'S THE FUTURE.
MY PARENTS.
MY COWORKERS.
MY GIRLFRIEND.
I'LL NEVER SEE
ANY OF THEM AGAIN.
YA-HOO!
[ Spooky Tremolo ]
WELCOME!
TO THE WORLD OF TOMORROW!
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO SAY IT THAT WAY?
HAVEN'T YOU EVER HEARD OF A
LITTLE THING CALLED SHOWMANSHIP?
[ Tremolo ]
COME! YOUR DESTINY AWAITS!
HAVE A NICE FUTURE.
COOL. JUST LIKE IN STAR TREK.
OH!
GOOD AFTERNOON. SIR.
MMM...
[ Gasps ]
NAME?
UH... FRY.
I'M LEELA.
NOW. IT'S NEW YEAR'S EVE
SO I'D LIKE TO DECIDE
YOUR FATE QUICKLY
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
AS LONG AS IT'S NOT
ABOUT MY EYE.
UH...
IS IT ABOUT MY EYE?
SORT OF.
[ Sighs ]
JUST ASK THE QUESTION.
WHAT'S WITH THE EYE?
I'M AN ALIEN.
ALL RIGHT?
LET'S DROP
THE SUBJECT.
COOL. AN ALIEN.
HAS YOUR RACE TAKEN
OVER THE EARTH?
NO. I JUST WORK HERE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS THAT BLIMP
ACCURATE?
YUP. IT'S
DECEMBER 31. 2999.
MY GOD.
A MILLION YEARS.
I'M SURE THIS MUST
BE VERY UPSETTING FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW. I GUESS
IT SHOULD BE
BUT ACTUALLY I'M GLAD.
I HAD NOTHING TO LIVE
FOR IN MY OLD LIFE.
I WAS BROKE.
I HAD A HUMILIATING JOB
AND I WAS BEGINNING TO SUSPECT
MY GIRLFRIEND
MIGHT BE CHEATING ON ME.
WELL. AT LEAST HERE
YOU'LL BE TREATED WITH DIGNITY.
NOW. STRIP NAKED AND GET
ON THE PROBULATOR.
OOH!
INTERESTING.
YOUR DNA TEST SHOWS
ONE LIVING RELATIVE.
HE'S YOUR GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GREAT-GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GREAT NEPHEW.
THAT'S GREAT. WHAT'S
THE LITTLE GUY'S NAME?
PROFESSOR HUBERT FARNSWORTH.
EW.
YOU KNOW. I'M THE LUCKIEST
GUY IN THE WHOLE FUTURE.
I'VE BEEN GIVEN A SECOND CHANCE
AND THIS TIME. I'M NOT GOING
TO BE A TOTAL LOSER.
WHAT'S THAT?
YOUR PERMANENT
CAREER ASSIGNMENT.
DELIVERY BOY?
NO! NOT AGAIN.
PLEASE. ANYTHING ELSE.
TAKE YOUR HANDS
OFF ME.
YOU'VE BEEN ASSIGNED
THE JOB YOU'RE BEST AT
JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
WHAT IF I REFUSE?
- THEN YOU'LL BE FIRED.
- FINE.
OUT OF A CANNON
INTO THE SUN.
- BUT I DON'T LIKE
BEING A DELIVERY BOY.
- WELL. THAT'S TOUGH.
LOTS OF PEOPLE
DON'T LIKE THEIR JOBS
BUT WE DO THEM ANYWAY.
"YOU GOTTA DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO."
NOW HOLD OUT YOUR HAND.
I'M GOING TO IMPLANT
YOUR CAREER CHIP.
IT'LL PERMANENTLY LABEL YOU
AS A DELIVERY BOY.
KEEP THAT THING AWAY FROM ME.
HOLD STILL. DAMN IT!
I DON'T HAVE
GOOD DEPTH PERCEPTION.
YOU'VE GOT TO THE COUNT OF FIVE
TO LET ME OUT OF HERE.
ONE...
SEE YOU IN A THOUSAND YEARS.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
YOU OWE ME ONE.
[ Grunts ]
WHOA.
RADIO CITY MUTANT HALL.
COOL.
UH. CROSS-TOWN EXPRESS.
[ Shrieks ]
[ Fry ]
WHOO-HOO!
YAAH...
[ Laughing ]
WHOO-HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO!
[ Shrieking ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Fry Yelling ]
OOMP!
[ Scoffing ]
PFFT.
TOURIST.
HEY. A PHONE BOOTH.
I CAN CALL MY NEPHEW.
WHOA. A REAL-LIVE ROBOT.
OR IS THAT SOME KIND
OF CHEESY NEW YEAR'S COSTUME?
BITE MY SHINY METAL ASS.
IT DOESN'T LOOK
SO SHINY TO ME.
SHINIER THAN YOURS. MEAT BAG.
[ Whistling ]
LISTEN. BUDDY. I'M
IN A HURRY HERE.
LET'S TRY FOR A TWOFER.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Woman ]
PLEASE SELECT MODE OF DEATH:
"QUICK AND PAINLESS"
OR "SLOW AND HORRIBLE."
YEAH. I'D LIKE TO
PLACE A COLLECT CALL.
YOU HAVE SELECTED
"SLOW AND HORRIBLE."
GREAT CHOICE.
BRING IT ON. BABY!
[ Shrieking ]
COME ON. COME ON!
KILL ME ALREADY.
BY THE WAY.
MY NAME'S BENDER.
HELP! WHAT'S
HAPPENING?
[ Woman ]
YOU ARE NOW DEAD.
THANK YOU FOR USING
STOP-AND-DROP--
AMERICA'S FAVORITE
SUICIDE BOOTH SINCE 2008.
[ Gasping For Air ]
LOUSY. STINKING RIP-OFF.
WELL. I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
ELSE PLANNED FOR TODAY.
LET'S GO GET DRUNK.
TWO. THREE... HEY.
[ Man ]
WELCOME TO
THE WORLD OF TOMORROW.
SHUT UP. TERRY.
THIS IS
UNACCEPTABLE. LEELA.
YOU MUST FIND THIS MR. FRY
AND INSTALL HIS CHIP.
LOOK. HE'S JUST A NOBODY
WHO DOESN'T WANT
TO BE A DELIVERY BOY.
I'D REALLY RATHER NOT
FORCE IT ON HIM.
WELL. THAT'S YOUR JOB
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT
AND IT'S MY JOB
TO MAKE YOU DO YOUR JOB
WHETHER I LIKE IT OR NOT--
WHICH I DO... VERY MUCH.
NOW. GET TO WORK!
[ Sighs ]
LIFE IS GOOD.
[ Gulping ]
WHY WOULD A ROBOT
NEED TO DRINK?
I DON'T NEED
TO DRINK.
I CAN QUIT
ANYTIME I WANT.
[ Burps ]
SO. THEY MADE YOU
A DELIVERY BOY. HUH?
MAN. THAT'S AS BAD AS MY JOB.
REALLY? WHAT DO YOU DO. BENDER?
I'M A BENDER-- I BEND GIRDERS.
THAT'S ALL I'M PROGRAMMED TO DO.
YOU ANY GOOD AT IT?
YOU KIDDING?
I WAS A STUD.
I COULD BEND A GIRDER
TO ANY ANGLE.
30 DEGREES...
32 DEGREES...
YOU NAME IT.
31... BUT I COULDN'T
GO ON LIVING
ONCE I FOUND OUT
WHAT THE GIRDERS
WERE FOR.
WHAT?
SUICIDE BOOTHS.
WELL. FRY. IT WAS
A PLEASURE MEETING YOU.
I'M GOING TO
GO KILL MYSELF.
WAIT...
YOU'RE THE ONLY FRIEND I HAVE.
YOU REALLY WANT A ROBOT
FOR A FRIEND?
YEAH. EVER SINCE I WAS SIX.
WELL. OKAY.
BUT I DON'T WANT
PEOPLE THINKING
WE'RE ROBOSEXUALS
SO IF ANYONE ASKS.
YOU'RE MY DE-BUGGER.
OH. NO. IT'S THE CYCLOPS.
DON'T LOOK.
DON'T LOOK!
I'M NOT LOOKING.
[ Gasps ]
THIS IS OFFICER 1-B-D-I
REQUESTING BACKUP.
WE'LL BE THERE
IN FIVE MINUTES.
[ Both Panting ]
WE CAN HIDE IN HERE.
IT'S FREE ON TUESDAYS.
WELCOME TO THE HEAD MUSEUM.
I'M LEONARD NIMOY.
SPOCK?
HEY. DO THE THING.
[ Chuckling ]
I DON'T DO THAT ANYMORE.
THIS IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
WHAT DO YOU HEADS
DO ALL DAY?
WE SHARE OUR WISDOM
WITH THOSE WHO SEEK IT.
IT'S A LIFE OF QUIET DIGNITY.
FEEDING TIME.
HMM...
I'M SORRY. FRY
BUT I HAVE TO INSTALL
YOUR CAREER CHIP.
YEAH. WELL IF YOU'RE SORRY
THEN WHY ARE YOU DOING IT?
IT'S MY JOB.
YOU GOTTA DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
[ All Groan In Fear ]
WATCH IT.
[ Nixon's Voice ]
THAT'S IT.
YOU JUST MADE MY LIST.
[ Growls ]
OW. OOH. OW. OW. OOH!
STOP IT!
DOWN BOY!
BAD PRESIDENT.
ALL RIGHT. BUDDY.
STEP AWAY FROM THE HEAD.
I'M GOING TO GET
24th CENTURY
ON HIS ASS.
[ Grunting ]
PLEASE. OFFICERS.
THERE'S NO NEED TO USE FORCE.
LET US HANDLE THIS.
WEIRDIE.
OH. COME ON.
HE'S JUST A POOR KID
FROM THE STUPID AGES.
KEEP YOUR BIG NOSE
OUT OF THIS. EYEBALL.
NO ONE MAKES FUN OF MY NOSE.
YEE-AAH!
OOH!
DAMN.
YOU GUYS WERE
TOTALLY OUT
OF CONTROL.
THAT'S OUR JOB.
WE'RE PEACE OFFICERS.
YEAH. YOU KNOW THE LAW--
YOU GOTTA DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
OH. WE'RE TRAPPED.
[ Grunts ]
WAIT A SECOND.
YOU'RE A BENDER. RIGHT?
WE CAN GET
OUT OF HERE
IF YOU JUST
BEND THE BARS.
DREAM ON. SKIN TUBE.
I'M ONLY PROGRAMMED TO BEND
FOR CONSTRUCTIVE PURPOSES.
WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE?
A DE-BENDER?
WHO CARES WHAT YOU'RE
PROGRAMMED FOR.
IF SOMEONE PROGRAMMED YOU
TO JUMP OFF A BRIDGE
WOULD YOU DO IT?
I'LL HAVE TO
CHECK MY PROGRAM.
YEP.
[ Leela ]
OPEN UP.
COME ON. BENDER.
IT'S UP TO YOU
TO MAKE
YOUR OWN DECISIONS IN LIFE.
THAT'S WHAT SEPARATES
PEOPLE AND ROBOTS
FROM ANIMALS
AND ANIMAL ROBOTS.
YOU'RE FULL
OF CRAP. FRY.
[ Spluttering ]
YOU MAKE A PERSUASIVE
ARGUMENT. FRY.
[ Grunting And Groaning ]
COME ON. BENDER.
YOU CAN DO IT.
CAN'T...
I CAN'T DO IT.
YES!
[ Laughing ]
YOU WERE RIGHT. FRY.
FROM NOW ON.
I'M GOING TO BEND WHAT I WANT
WHEN I WANT. WHO I WANT.
I AM UNSTOPPABLE!
AAH.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
YOU DID THAT.
[ Leela ]
YEE-AAH!
[ Yells ]
WAIT!
[ Bender ]
NO. THANKS.
LOOKS LIKE ONE OF US WILL
HAVE TO BEND THIS GRATE.
OH.
[ Chuckling ]
GOOD LORD.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S THE DECAYING RUINS
OF OLD NEW YORK.
WELCOME HOME. PAL.
IT'S MY OLD
NEIGHBORHOOD.
MAN. THIS BRINGS BACK
A LOT OF MEMORIES.
KEEP 'EM TO
YOURSELF. POPS.
THIS IS WHERE
I BROUGHT MY GIRLFRIEND
ON OUR VERY FIRST DATE.
MY GOD.
SHE'S GONE.
EVERYONE I EVER KNEW
OR CARED ABOUT IS GONE.
WAIT. THERE'S
SOMEONE YOU KNOW.
OH... CAN'T YOU
LEAVE ME ALONE?
I'M MISERABLE
ENOUGH ALREADY.
LOOK. I KNOW IT'S
NOT MUCH CONSOLATION
BUT I UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU FEEL.
NO. YOU DON'T.
I'VE GOT NO HOME. NO FAMILY.
NO FRIENDS.
MY WHOLE WORLD IS GONE.
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY
UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
TO BE SO ALONE.
I UNDERSTAND.
I'M THE ONLY ONE-EYED ALIEN
ON THIS WHOLE PLANET.
MY PARENTS ABANDONED ME HERE
AS A BABY
AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT GALAXY THEY WERE FROM.
I KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO BE ALONE.
LOOK. LEELA
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS WORLD.
BUT... YOU OBVIOUSLY DO
SO I GIVE UP.
IF YOU REALLY THINK I SHOULD
BE A DELIVERY BOY. I'LL DO IT.
[ Groans ]
YOUR CHIP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
QUITTING.
WHY?
BECAUSE I'VE
ALWAYS WANTED TO.
I JUST NEVER REALIZED IT
UNTIL I MET YOU.
WHAT IS THE
MATTER WITH YOU?
I JUST WANTED TO BE
PART OF THE MOMENT.
HEY! HE STOLE
MY RING.
SORRY.
WELL. THAT SOLVES THE MYSTERY
OF THE MISSING RING.
THIS CALLS FOR A DRINK.
I DON'T WANT
TO SPOIL THE PARTY
BUT WE'RE ALL
JOB DESERTERS NOW.
WE'RE UNEMPLOYED
AND WE HAVE NOWHERE TO GO.
CORRECTION:
WE'RE UNEMPLOYED
BUT WE HAVE A DODDERING OLD
RELATIVE TO MOOCH OFF OF.
[ Snoring ]
HELLO. I'M DICK CLARK'S HEAD.
WELCOME TO A SPECIAL
YEAR 3000 EDITION
OF NEW YEAR'S ROCKIN' EVE.
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Gasping ]
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M YOUR DEAR
OLD UNCLE FRY.
I DON'T HAVE AN UNCLE FRY.
YOU DO NOW.
BY GOD. I AM
YOUR NEPHEW.
THIS IS ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
CAN WE HAVE
SOME MONEY?
OH. MY. NO.
LET ME SHOW YOU AROUND.
THAT'S MY LAB TABLE AND
THIS IS MY WORK STOOL
AND OVER THERE IS MY
INTERGALACTIC SPACESHIP
AND HERE'S WHERE I KEEP
ASSORTED LENGTHS OF WIRE.
[ Fry ]
WHOA.
A REAL LIVE SPACESHIP.
I DESIGNED IT MYSELF.
LET ME SHOW YOU
SOME OF THE DIFFERENT
LENGTHS OF WIRE I USED.
ATTENTION. JOB DESERTERS!
COME OUT WITH YOUR HANDS UP!
WE HAVE YOU
PARTIALLY SURROUNDED.
NO!
GET THOSE BUMS.
WELL. WE'RE BONED.
CAN'T WE GET AWAY
IN THE SHIP?
I SUPPOSE IT IS
TECHNICALLY POSSIBLE
THOUGH I AM ALREADY
IN MY PAJAMAS.
I'LL GET US OUT OF HERE.
CAN ANYONE DRIVE STICK?
I CAN--
AS LONG AS I DON'T
HAVE TO PARALLEL PARK.
IF THEY TRY TO TAKE OFF.
GIVE 'EM AN ASS FULL OF LASER.
PREPARE FOR LIFTOFF.
TEN...
[ Crowd ]
NINE!
AMANIA!
SEVEN!
[ Gurgling ]
FIVE!
FOUR.
THREE.
TWO.
ONE!
BLAST OFF!
[ Crowds Cheering ]
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
FIRE. FIRE!
I CAN'T SEE NOTHIN'.
PRETTY. THOUGH.
W-WHA-- HEY.
HEY! WHOA!
PHEW.
[ Fry ]
YEAH!
[ Cheering ]
SO. I GUESS WITHOUT JOBS.
WE'LL BE FUGITIVES FOREVER.
NOT NECESSARILY.
ARE YOU THREE.
BY ANY CHANCE
INTERESTED IN BECOMING
MY NEW SPACESHIP CREW?
NEW CREW?
WELL. WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE OLD CREW?
OH. THOSE POOR SONS OF--
BUT THAT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS.
I NEED A NEW CREW.
ANYONE INTERESTED?
YES. YES!
THAT'S EXACTLY THE JOB
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED.
THANKS FOR THE
OFFER. PROFESSOR
BUT WE DON'T HAVE THE
PROPER CAREER CHIPS.
OH. THAT WON'T BE A PROBLEM.
AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT.
I SAVED THE CHIPS
FROM MY PREVIOUS CREW.
THIS IS AWESOME.
ARE WE GOING
TO FLY THROUGH SPACE
FIGHTING MONSTERS AND TEACHING
ALIEN WOMEN TO LOVE?
IF BY THAT YOU MEAN
TRANSPORTING CARGO. THEN YES.
IT'S A LITTLE HOME BUSINESS
I STARTED TO FUND MY RESEARCH.
COOL. WHAT'S MY JOB GOING TO BE?
YOU'LL BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR ENSURING THAT THE CARGO
REACHES ITS
DESTINATION.
SO... I'M GOING TO BE A...
DELIVERY BOY?
EXACTLY.
ALL RIGHT!
I'M A DELIVERY BOY!